# **LINDSEY DUBNICKA**

Milwaukee, WI |507-219-7479 | lindseymiller2567@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/lindseydubnicka | GitHub: https://github.com/lindseymiller2567

Portfolio: <a href="https://lindseymiller2567.github.io/react-portfolio">https://lindseymiller2567.github.io/react-portfolio</a>

# **PROFILE**

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in the graphic arts, and newly developed skills in JavaScript, React, and backend technologies such as MySQL, GraphQL and NodeJS. Earned a certificate in full stack web development from the University of Wisconsin.

Successfully collaborated with a development team to create an interactive web application that lets users connect with one another about various ideas or problems they may have with caring for their house plants. With each project, I strive to create a meaningful web experience for the end-user while also writing clean and organized code that follows ES6 best practices. Known as a detail-oriented and tech-savvy professional with a strategic vision to harness team creativity and work toward innovating solutions.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks & Libraries: Bootstrap, Express.js, React, Mongoose, Sequelize

Other: Restful APIs, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, GitHub, GraphQL, Apollo server, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator,

Microsoft Office

### **PROJECTS**

#### **Propagatorz**

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/alinz07/Propagatorz">https://github.com/alinz07/Propagatorz</a> | Deployed: <a href="https://propagatorz-plant-help.herokuapp.com">https://propagatorz-plant-help.herokuapp.com</a>

- Web application that allows users to seek advice from other users on their house plants.
- Collaborated with a team of four. Responsible for setting up the models, creating the GraphQL schemas,
   implementing the frontend using React and the MUI CSS Library, and setting up Cloudinary to store the user's uploaded images.
- Technologies Used: Node.js, Express.js, React, MongoDB, Mongoose, GraphQL, Apollo server, Cloudinary API, JavaScript, MUI CSS Library

#### **Bookworm**

GitHub: https://github.com/Hmlessard/Bookworm | Deployed: https://asgardians-bookworm.herokuapp.com

- Blog-style web application for booklovers to come together to share thoughts and discuss their favorite books. Requires users to log-in or sign up to participate in discussions.
- Worked with a team of three to create a web app using MVC architecture pattern. Responsible for setting up the models, creating some of the API routes, and styling the page.
- Technologies Used: Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Handlebars.js, Bcrypt, session storage, Book Cover Web API, JavaScript, Bootstrap

### **Dinner Party Planner**

GitHub: https://github.com/MattKolbach/DinnerPlanner | Deployed: https://mattkolbach.github.io/DinnerPlanner

- Client-side web application that lets users search through dinner and drink recipes to help them prepare the perfect spread for an upcoming dinner party.
- Joined forces with a team of three other developers to create a web app using third party API's. In charge of the
  overall UI and implementing the Pure CSS Library. Contributed to the feature that allows users to save their
  favorite recipes.
- Technologies Used: JavaScript, Pure CSS, TheCocktailDB Web API, TheMealDB Web API, local storage

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Catalog Print Project Coordinator**

Arandell Corporation | Menomonee Falls, WI | July 2019 - Present

- Oversee catalog print projects throughout the manufacturing process while managing client relationships.
- Work with internal departments to help those involved gain alignment on client's needs and requirements.
- Contribute to the company's internal software development by testing new software features, and participating in workflow improvement meetings.
- Conceptualized and helped implement a job tracker that keeps track of all major milestones, tasks and due dates of a project throughout the project's lifecycle.
- Enhance the department's training program while participating on a team that creates best practice documents.

#### **Packaging Graphics Project Coordinator**

Schawk | Minneapolis, MN | December 2015 - September 2018

- Managed and coordinated anywhere from 30–80+ projects simultaneously in a fast-paced environment, paying attention to all details to ensure each project's success.
- Built relationships with and maintained direct contact for clients, internal departments and vendors on current projects to ensure alignment of goals, process and expected results.
- Directed packaging artwork fulfillment processes from initial concept and design through pre-press for various international brands.
- Ensured all brand standards were met throughout design and production art stages to ensure the delivery of a superior product.
- Created project timelines and ensured deadlines were met by coordinating with key project stakeholders, including designers, production artists, scheduling managers and clients. Utilized creative problem solving collaboration meetings to overcome roadblocks and detours that could have put the project at risk for on-time delivery of a quality product.
- Reviewed and evaluated electronic graphic art and supporting files, such as fonts, images, and vector files, for print readiness.

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Certificate | UW-Extended Campus Coding Boot Camp November 2021 - May 2022

Graphic Communications Management, Bachelors | UW-Stout | Menomonie, WI September 2011 - June 2015